Guide to the Carmel Bach Festival Tape Collection ARS.0025
Archive of Recorded Sound
Carmel Bach Festival Tape Collection
1962-1982
ARS.0025
Archive of Recorded Sound
13.1 Linear feet 190 open reel audio tapes and 20 audiocassettes
London, Jack, 1876 - 1916
Access Restrictions
None.
Provenance
Purchase, 1940; gift of Felton Elkins, 1942; gift of Christian deGuigne, 1964; and gift of Arnold G. Applegarth, 1986.
Biography
Jack London was born in San Francisco January 12, 1876. He led an adventurous life, only beginning his career as an author in the 1890s. He wrote short stories, serials, essays, articles, verse and novels. He died November 22, 1916 in Sonoma County, CA.
Scope and Content
Chiefly letters by London to Mabel and Edward M. Applegarth; to his English literary agent, James B. Pinker; and to his daughters. Also includes manuscripts of two longer works and nine poems by London, five poems by Edward Applegarth, several letters and postcards by Charmian London, and photographs. There is an ink wash painting by Maynard Dixon done for London's SON OF WOLF.
London, Charmian.; Dixon, Maynard.; Applegarth, Mabel.; Applegarth, J.H.; Porter, W.S.; Applegarth, Edward M.; Pinker, James B.; London, Jack, 1876-1916.; American literature--20th century.; Photoprints.; London, Jack, 1876-1916--Photographs.; Authors, American--20th century.
- Concert, 07/20/1962; CBF001-CBF003; 3 7"open reel audio tapes
  - Magnificat in D major, with Christmas interpolations from original version, 07/20/1962; CBF001; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Baggott, Ruth; Chase, Jennifer; Di Tullio, Louise; Gibson, Marie, singer; Law, Pauline; Lindsay, Mary Esther; Linsley, Ralph; Paul, Thomas, 1934-; Phillips, Barbara; Riffel, Richard; Sorensen, Katherine; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Andrews, Richard, harpsichordist (Reel CBF001)
    General note
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Magnificat, BWV 243, D major
    Christmas music; Magnificats (Music)
  - Brandenburg concerto no. 4 in G major, 07/20/1962; CBF002; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Sterne, Colin; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Waller, Rosemary; Sterne, Roberta (Reel CBF002)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Brandenburgische Konzerte. Nr. 4.
    Concerti grossi
  - Concerto for three claviers and strings in C major, 07/20/1962; CBF002; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Washington, Eileen; Linsley, Ralph; Ehlers, Alice, 1887-1981; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 (Reel CBF002)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Concertos, harpsichords (3), string orchestra, BWV 1064, C major
    Concertos (Harpsichord ensemble with string orchestra)
  - Sacred cantata no. 50, Nun ist das Heil, 07/20/1962; CBF003; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 (Reel CBF003)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Nun ist das Heil und die Kraft
    Choruses, Sacred (Mixed voices) with orchestra; Cantatas, Sacred
- Influence of opera on music of the 17th and 18th centuries, 07/21/1962; CBF004-CBF006; 3.0 open reel tapes
  - Sonata for trumpet and double string orchestra, 07/21/1962; CBF004; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Haug, Edward; Stradella, Alessandro, 1639-1682 (Reel CBF004)
    Uniform title
    Stradella, Alessandro, 1639-1682. Sonatas, viols (8), trumpet, continuo, G. 7.4-3, D major; arr.
    Trumpet with string orchestra
  - Concerto for piccolo and strings, F. VI, no. 4 in C major, 07/21/1962; CBF004; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Di Tullio, Louise; Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741 (Reel CBF004)
    Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741. Concertos, recorder, string orchestra, RV 443, C major
    Concertos (Piccolo with string orchestra)
  - Combiatimento de Tancredi e Clorinda, 07/21/1962; CBF005; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Monteverdi, Claudio, 1567-1643; Tippey, James; Loper, Robert; Bressler, Charles; Bischoff, Colleen (Reel CBF005)
    Combattimento di Tancredi e Clorinda
    Madrigals, Italian; Operas
  - Je c\u00E8de \u00E0 vos d\u00E9sirs-- D'une image, h\u00E9las (Iphig\u00E9nie en Tauride), 07/21/1962; CBF006; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Gluck, Christoph Willibald, Ritter von, 1714-1787; Bischoff, Colleen (Reel CBF006)
    Iphig\u00E9nie en Tauride. D'une image, h\u00E9las
    Operas--Excerpts
  - Or sai chi l'onore (Don Giovanni), 07/21/1962; CBF006; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791; Bischoff, Colleen (Reel CBF006)
    Don Giovanni. Or sai, chi l'onore
  - "Haffner" Symphony, no. 35, K. 385 in D major, 07/21/1962; CBF006; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791 (Reel CBF006)
    Symphonies, K. 385, D major
    Scope and Contents note
    Allegro con spirito -- Andante -- Menuetto -- Finale: Presto
    Symphonies
- The passion of our Lord according to St. Matthew, 07/22/1962; CBF007-CBF012; 6 7 in. open reel audio tapes; Festival Chorale.; Grimes, Bruce; Bennett, Leon; Cabral, Herbert; Ballengee, Edward; Bardi, Gina; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Toews, Theodore; Bach Festival Chorus.; Tippey, James; Smart, La Vonne; Schwabacher, James, Jr.; Schlinger, Katharine; Remsberg, Bruce; Janzen, Stephen (Reel CBF012, Reel CBF007, Reel CBF010)
  Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Matth\u00E4uspassion
  Passion music; Oratorios
- Flowering of the late Baroque orchestral style in the works of J.S. Bach, 07/23/1962; CBF013-CBF016; 4 7 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Brandenburg concerto no. 5 in D major, 07/23/1965; CBF013; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Waller, Rosemary; Di Tullio, Louise; Ehlers, Alice, 1887-1981; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 (Reel CBF013)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Brandenburgische Konzerte. Nr. 5
  - Sacred cantata no. 152, Tritt auf die Glaubensbahn, 07/23/1962; CBF014; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Gibson, Marie, singer; Dust\u00E9, Raymond; Trampler, Walter; Heinitz, Eva; Sterne, Colin (Reel CBF014)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Tritt auf die Glaubensbahn
  - Brandenburg concerto no. 1 in F major, 07/23/1962; CBF016; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Waller, Rosemary; Bergstone, Fred; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Kates, Philip; Dust\u00E9, Raymond; Taylor, Ross, arranger; Price, Charles Gower, 1939- (Reel CBF016)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Brandenburgische Konzerte. Nr. 1
- Concerto and concerto grosso, 07/24/1962; CBF017-CBF019; 3 7 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Brandenburg Concerto no. 3 in G major, 07/24/1962; CBF017; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Witte, Robert; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Waller, Rosemary; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Cox, John; Dessler, Ellen; Han-Gorski, Adam; Hall, Thomas; Roberts, Charles; Imes, Marjorie (Reel CBF017)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Brandenburgische Konzerte. Nr. 3
  - Concerto for oboe, op. 7, no. 6, 07/24/1962; CBF017; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Albinoni, Tomaso, 1671-1750; Dust\u00E9, Raymond (Reel CBF017)
    Concertos, op. 7. No. 6
    Concertos (Oboe with string orchestra)
  - Brandenburg Concerto no. 2 in F major, 07/24/1962; CBF018; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Dust\u00E9, Raymond; Haug, Edward; Sterne, Colin; Waller, Rosemary (Reel CBF018)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Brandenburgische Konzerte. Nr. 2
  - Sacred cantata no. 106, Gottes Zeit ist die allerbeste Zeit, 07/24/1962; CBF018; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Andrews, Richard, harpsichordist; Lindsay, Mary Esther; Festival Chorale.; Linsley, Ralph; Dessler, Ellen; Schwabacher, James, Jr.; Baggott, Ruth; Tippey, James; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 (Reel CBF018)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Gottes Zeit ist die allerbeste Zeit
  - Concerto for piano and orchestra, no. 24, K. 491, in C minor, 07/24/1962; CBF019; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Stravinsky, Soulima, 1910-1994; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791 (Reel CBF019)
    Concertos, piano, orchestra, K. 491, C minor
    Concertos (Piano)
- Jephtha: an oratorio, 07/26/1962; CBF020-CBF022; 3 7 in. open reel audio tapes; Brooks, Carol, singer; Bressler, Charles; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Stanford, Carolyn; Bach Festival Chorus.; Remsberg, Bruce; Phillips, Barbara; Law, Pauline; Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759 (Reel CBF021, Reel CBF020)
  Jephtha
  Oratorios; Choruses, Sacred (Mixed voices) with orchestra
- Concert, 07/27/1962; CBF023-CBF025; 3 7 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Magnificat, 07/27/1962; CBF023; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 (Reel CBF023)
    Choruses, Sacred (Mixed voices) with orchestra; Magnificats (Music)
  - Brandenburg concerto no. 4 in G major, 07/27/1962; CBF024; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 (Reel CBF024)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Brandenburgische Konzerte. Nr. 4
  - Concerto for 3 claviers in C major, 07/27/1962; CBF024; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 (Reel CBF024)
    Concertos (Harpsichords (3) with string orchestra)
  - Sacred cantata no. 50, 07/27/1962; CBF025; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 (Reel CBF025)
- Influence of opera on music of the 17th and 18th centuries, 07/28/1962; CBF026-CBF028; 3.0 7" open reel tapes
  - Sonata for trumpet and double string orchestra, 07/28/1962; CBF026; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Haug, Edward; Stradella, Alessandro, 1639-1682 (Reel CBF026)
  - Concerto for piccolo and strings, V. VI, no. 4 in C major, 07/28/1962; CBF026; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Di Tullio, Louise; Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741 (Reel CBF026)
  - Combiatimento di Tancredi e Clorinda, 07/28/1962; CBF026; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Bischoff, Colleen; Monteverdi, Claudio, 1567-1643; Tippey, James; Bressler, Charles; Loper, Robert (Reel CBF026)
  - Je c\u00E8de \u00E0 vos d\u00E9sirs-- D'une image h\u00E9las!: from Iphig\u00E9nie en Tauride, 07/28/1962; CBF028; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Gluck, Christoph Willibald, Ritter von, 1714-1787; Bischoff, Colleen (Reel CBF028)
  - Or sai chi l'onore, from Don Giovanni, 07/28/1962; CBF028; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791; Bischoff, Colleen (Reel CBF028)
  - Haffner symphony, no. 35, K. 385 in D major, 07/28/1962; CBF028; 1 7 in. open reel audio tape; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791 (Reel CBF028)
- The passion of our Lord according to St. Matthew, 07/29/1962; CBF029-CBF034; 6 7" open reel audio tapes; Schwabacher, James, Jr.; Schlinger, Katharine; Tippey, James; Smart, La Vonne; Toews, Theodore; Bach Festival Chorus.; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Bardi, Gina; Ballengee, Edward; Cabral, Herbert; Bennett, Leon; Grimes, Bruce; Festival Chorale.; Remsberg, Bruce; Janzen, Stephen (Reel CBF034, Reel CBF032, Reel CBF033)
- Works of J. S. Bach, 07/16/1965; CBF035-CBF036; 2.0 10" open reel tapes
  - Sacred cantata no. 1, "Wie schoen leuchtet der Morgenstern", 07/16/1965; CBF035; 1 10 in. open reel audio tape; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Bogard, Carole; Felber, William, bass; Festival Chorale.; Goleeke, Tom; Bach Festival Chorus.; Bach Festival Orchestra. (Reel CBF035)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Wie sch\u00F6n leuchtet der Morgenstern (Cantata)
    Cantatas, Sacred; Choruses, Sacred (Mixed voices) with orchestra
  - Concerto for harpsichord, recorders and strings in F major. Allegro -- Andante, 07/16/1965; CBF035-CBF036; 2 10 in. open reel audio tapes; Continues on CBF036; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Linsley, Ralph; Sterne, Colin; Sterne, Roberta (Reel CBF036, Reel CBF035)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Concertos, harpsichord, orchestra, BWV 1057, F major
    Concertos (Harpsichord)
  - Magnificat in D major, 07/16/1965; CBF036; 1 10 in. open reel audio tape; Law, Pauline; Varga, Lois, mezzo-soprano; Bach Festival Chorus.; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Berberian, Ara; Gibson, Marie, singer; Goleeke, Tom; Jameson, Edward, tenor (Reel CBF036)
    Magnificats (Music); Choruses, Sacred (Mixed voices) with orchestra
- The passion of our Lord according to St. Matthew, 07/18/1965; CBF039-CBF042; 4 10 in. open reel audio tapes (Reel CBF040, Reel CBF039, Reel CBF042)
- Orfeo, a fable in music, 07/17/1965; CBF037-CBF038; 2 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tapes; Salgo, Sandor; Burch, Carole, singer; Bressler, Charles; Felber, William, bass; Cariaga, Marvellee, singer; Gibson, Marie, singer; Festival Chorale.; Hodges, Norma Jean; Goleeke, Tom; Holcomb, Arthur, singer; Hull, James, singer; Jameson, Edward, tenor; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Law, Pauline; Layng, Jacquelyn, singer; Berberian, Ara; Monteverdi, Claudio, 1567-1643; Bailey, Eleanor, singer; Oliver, Robert, singer; Bogard, Carole; Olson, Robert, singer; Bernard, Robert, singer (Reel CBF038, Reel CBF037)
  Orfeo
  Operas
- Bach's soloists: sonata to concerto, 07/20/1965; CBF046-CBF048; 3 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Sonata for flute and harpsichord no.1, in B minor, 07/22/1965; CBF046; Ehlers, Alice, 1887-1981; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Shanley, Gretel
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Sonatas, flute, harpsichord, BWV 1030, B minor
    Sonatas (Flute and harpsichord)
  - Sonata for solo violin no.1, in G minor, 07/22/1965; CBF046; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Shapiro, Eudice
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Sonaten und Partiten, violin, BWV 1001-1006. Sonata, no. 1
  - Sacred cantata no. 32, Liebster Jesu, mein Verlangen, 07/22/1965; CBF047; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Bach Festival Chorus.; Berberian, Ara; Gibson, Marie, singer (Reel CBF047)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Liebster Jesu, mein Verlangen
  - Concerto in the Italian style, 07/22/1965; CBF048; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Ehlers, Alice, 1887-1981; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 (Reel CBF048)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Italienisches Konzert
  - Brandenburg concerto no.6, in B flat major, 07/22/1965; CBF048; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Heinitz, Eva; Linsley, Ralph; Bresler, Mary, double bass player; Dessler, Ellen; Persinger, Rolf; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Lufkin, Dennis, violist; Miloradovitch, Hazelle (Reel CBF048)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Brandenburgische Konzerte. Nr. 6
- The Italian concerto and its culmination, 07/22/1965; CBF049-CBF049a;CBF050; 3 10 1/2 in.open reel audio tapes
  - Concerto in E flat major, La tempesta di mare, for violin and strings., 07/22/1965; CBF049; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Waller, Rosemary; Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741 (Reel CBF049)
    Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741. Cimento dell'armonia e dell'inventione. N. 5
    Concertos (Violin with string orchestra)
  - Sonata for two trumpets and strings., 07/22/1965; CBF049; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Bubb, Charles, trumpet player; Aldrovandini, Giuseppe, 1673-1707; Haug, Edward (Reel CBF049)
    Sinfonias, trumpets (2), string orchestra, D major
    Trumpets (2) with string orchestra
  - Concerto for viola da gamba and strings, 07/22/1965; CBF049a; Pfeiffer, Johann, 1697-1761; Heinitz, Eva
    Concertos, viola da gamba, string orchestra, A major
    Concertos (Viola da gamba with string orchestra)
  - Concerto K.503, in C major for piano and orchestra, 07/22/1965; CBF049a; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791
    Concertos, piano, orchestra, K. 503, C major
  - Cantata no. 211, Schweigt stille, plaudert nicht, 07/22/1965; CBF050; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape (Reel CBF050)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Kaffee-Kantate
    Cantatas, Secular; Choruses, Secular (Mixed voices) with orchestra
- Concert, Sunset Auditorium. Works of J. S. Bach (1685-1750), 07/23/1965; CBF051-CBF052; 2 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Sacred cantata no. 1, Wie schoen leuchtet der Morgenstern, 07/23/1965; CBF051; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Bogard, Carole; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Bach Festival Chorus.; Goleeke, Tom; Festival Chorale.; Felber, William, bass (Reel CBF051)
  - Concerto for harpsichord, recorders and strings in F major, 07/23/1965; CBF051; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Linsley, Ralph; Sterne, Colin; Sterne, Roberta (Reel CBF051)
  - Magnificat in D major, 07/23/1965; CBF052; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Berberian, Ara; Festival Chorale.; Gibson, Marie, singer; Goleeke, Tom; Jameson, Edward, tenor; Law, Pauline; Bach Festival Chorus.; Varga, Lois, mezzo-soprano; Bach Festival Orchestra. (Reel CBF052)
- Orfeo, a fable in music, 07/24/1965; CBF053-CBF054; 2 10 1/2" open reel audio tapes; Layng, Jacquelyn, singer; Berberian, Ara; Law, Pauline; Bernard, Robert, singer; Oliver, Robert, singer; Monteverdi, Claudio, 1567-1643; Bailey, Eleanor, singer; Holcomb, Arthur, singer; Hodges, Norma Jean; Jameson, Edward, tenor; Hull, James, singer; Festival Chorale.; Felber, William, bass; Goleeke, Tom; Gibson, Marie, singer; Olson, Robert, singer; Bressler, Charles; Salgo, Sandor; Bogard, Carole; Cariaga, Marvellee, singer; Burch, Carole, singer (Reel CBF054, Reel CBF053)
- The passion of our Lord according to St. Matthew, 07/25/1965; CBF055-CBF059; 5 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tapes; Festival Chorale.; Felber, William, bass; White, Arlene, singer; Faris, Robert, singer; Cabral, Herbert; Schwabacher, James, Jr.; Bernard, Robert, singer; Waterbury, Robert, singer; Berberian, Ara; Russo, Vincent, singer; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Schlinger, Katharine; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Layng, Jacquelyn, singer; Bach Festival Chorus.; Oliver, Robert, singer; Jameson, Edward, tenor; Law, Pauline; Gibson, Marie, singer; Grimes, Bruce; Feuerstein, William, singer; Flaherty, Marion, singer (Reel CBF057, Reel CBF058, Reel CBF059)
  Oratorios; Passion music
- Concert, Sunset School Auditorium, 07/15/1966; CBF060-CBF062; 3 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Sacred cantata no.11, Lobet Gott in seinen Reichen, 07/15/1966; CBF060; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; White, Orville, bass; Schwabacher, James, Jr.; Salgo, Sandor; Gibson, Marie, singer; Festival Chorale.; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Bach Festival Chorus.; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Allen, Betty, 1930-
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Lobet Gott in seinen Reichen
  - Concerto for flute in G major, 07/15/1966; CBF061; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Di Tullio, Louise; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 (Reel CBF061)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Concertos, flute, string orchestra, RV 436, G major
    Concertos (Flute with string orchestra)
  - Concerto for four violins, op.3, no.10, in B minor, 07/15/1966; CBF062; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741; Loban, John; Waller, Rosemary; Griffin, Doris, violin; Baddin, Melvin, violinist (Reel CBF062)
    Estro armonico. N. 10
    Concertos (Violins (4) with string orchestra)
  - Concerto for four claviers, in A minor, 07/15/1966; CBF062; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Ehlers, Alice, 1887-1981; Chaney, Harold; Linsley, Ralph; Hamilton, Malcolm (Reel CBF062)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Concertos, harpsichords (4), string orchestra, BWV 1065, A minor
  - Sacred cantata no. 50, Nun ist das Heil, 07/15/1966; CBF062; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Bach Festival Chorus.; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Festival Chorale. (Reel CBF062)
- Concert, Sunset School Auditorium, 07/16/1966; CBF063-CBF065; 3 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Brandenburg concerto no.5, in D major, 07/16/1966; CBF063; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Di Tullio, Louise; Ehlers, Alice, 1887-1981; Waller, Rosemary; Bach Festival Orchestra. (Reel CBF063)
  - The Game of Cards, 07/16/1966; CBF063; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Armstrong, Karen, soprano; Burch, Carole, singer; Caldara, Antonio, 1670-1736; Hodges, Norma Jean; Nicola, Mary Esther, soprano (Reel CBF063)
    Giuoco di quadriglio
    Choruses, Secular (Mixed voices) with orchestra; Cantatas, Secular
  - Concerto for violin, K.216, in G major, 07/16/1966; CBF064; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791; Abel, David, violinist (Reel CBF064)
    Concertos, violin, orchestra, K. 216, G major
    Concertos (Violin)
  - Symphony no. 39, K.543 in E flat major, 07/16/1966; CBF065; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791; Bach Festival Orchestra. (Reel CBF065)
    Symphonies, K. 543, E\u266D major
- The Mass in B minor, 07/17/1966; CBF066-CBF068; 3 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tapes; Gibson, Marie, singer; Festival Chorale.; Dunning, Edwin; Brown, Melvin; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Bach Festival Chorus.; Allen, Betty, 1930-; Law, Pauline (Reel CBF066, Reel CBF068, Reel CBF067)
  Uniform
  Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Masses, BWV 232, B minor
  Masses
- Concert, Sunset School Auditorium, 07/19/1966; CBF073-CBF-075; 3 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Concerto for oboe, violin and string orchestra in C minor, 07/19/1966; CBF073; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Abel, David, violinist; Dust\u00E9, Raymond; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 (Reel CBF073)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Concertos, harpsichords (2), string orchestra, BWV 1060, C minor; arr.
    Concertos (Oboe and violin with string orchestra), Arranged
  - Sacred Cantata no. 13, Meine Seufzer, meine Thraenen, 07/19/1966; CBF073; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Nicola, Mary Esther, soprano; Jameson, Edward, tenor; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Dunning, Edwin; Cariaga, Marvellee, singer (Reel CBF073)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Meine Seufzer, meine Tränen
  - Symphony no.93, in D major, 07/19/1966; CBF074; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Bach Festival Orchestra. (Reel CBF074)
    Symphonies, H. I, 93, D major
  - Concerto for piano, K. 482, in E flat major, 07/19/1966; CBF075; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Nádas, István (Reel CBF075)
    Concertos, piano, orchestra, K. 482, E\u266D major
- Athaliah, an oratorio, 07/21/1966; CBF076-CBF078; 3 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tapes; Law, Pauline; Bach Festival Chorus.; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Di Francesco, Michael, singer; Dunning, Edwin; Festival Chorale.; Gibson, Marie, singer; Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759; Jameson, Edward, tenor; Armstrong, Karen, soprano (Reel CBF078, Reel CBF077, Reel CBF076)
  Athalia
  Oratorios
- Concert, Sunset School Auditorium, 07/22/1966; CBF079-CBF081; 3 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tapes
  - Sacred Cantata no.11, Lobet Gott in seinen Reichen. Ascension Oratotio, 07/22/1966; CBF079; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Bernard, Robert, singer; Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; Bach Festival Orchestra.; Bach Festival Chorus.; Allen, Betty, 1930-; Festival Chorale.; Gibson, Marie, singer; Schwabacher, James, Jr. (Reel CBF079)
  - Concerto for flute in G major, 07/22/1966; CBF080; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Di Tullio, Louise; Bach, Carl Philipp Emanuel, 1714-1788; Bach Festival Orchestra. (Reel CBF080)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Concertos, flute, string orchestra, H. 445, G major
  - Concerto for four violins, op. 3, no. 10, in B minor, 07/22/1966; CBF081; 1 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tape; Waller, Rosemary; Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741; Loban, John; Griffin, Doris, violin; Baddin, Melvin, violinist; Bach Festival Orchestra. (Reel CBF081)
    Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741. Estro armonico. N. 10
- Concert, Sunset School Auditorium, 07/23/1966; CBF082-CBF084; 4 10 1/2 in. open reel audio tapes